<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
    <ThingDef Abstract="true" Name="GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase" ParentName="BaseMeleeWeapon_Sharp_Quality">
        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
        <graphicData>
            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
            <shaderType>CutoutComplex</shaderType>
        </graphicData>
        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
        <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
        <thingSetMakerTags><li>RewardStandardQualitySuper</li></thingSetMakerTags>
        <weaponTags>
            <li>IndustrialMeleeDecent</li>
            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
        </weaponTags>
        <stuffCategories>
			<li>Metallic</li>
		</stuffCategories>
        <tradeTags>
            <li>HPMelee</li>
            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
        </tradeTags>
        <relicChance>2</relicChance>
        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
        <recipeMaker>
            <researchPrerequisite>GW_Chainswords</researchPrerequisite>
            <recipeUsers Inherit="False">
                <li>HP_AM_MilitarumFabricationBench</li>
            </recipeUsers>
            <displayPriority>410</displayPriority>
            <skillRequirements>
                <Crafting>6</Crafting>
            </skillRequirements>
        </recipeMaker>
    </ThingDef>

<!-- ====================== Chainsword ===================== -->

    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainsword</defName>
        <label>Militarum Chainsword</label>
        <description>The Militarum Chainsword, a quintessential close combat weapon within the Astra Militarum's vast armory, epitomizes the Imperium's relentless determination in the face of close-quarters engagements within the brutal and unforgiving battles of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nThis formidable melee weapon is a chainsaw-like implement, featuring a chain of monomolecular teeth powered by a high-torque motor. The Militarum Chainsword's primary function is to deliver swift, brutal, and efficient strikes in hand-to-hand combat. With its buzzing teeth capable of tearing through armor, flesh, and bone, the Chainsword is a symbol of the Astra Militarum's unwavering commitment to close combat effectiveness.\n\nWielded by the courageous soldiers of the Imperium, the Militarum Chainsword serves as a testament to the gritty determination of the Astra Militarum in the face of the galaxy's countless horrors. In the melee chaos of the 41st millennium, the Chainsword becomes an extension of the guardsman's will, embodying the unyielding spirit of the Imperial Guard as they stand against the darkness.\n\nWhether charging headlong into the enemy ranks or used as a last line of defense in desperate situations, the Militarum Chainsword remains a stalwart companion to the courageous soldiers of the Astra Militarum, ready to deliver the Emperor's justice in the form of whirring blades and unyielding resolve.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/Chainsword</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <WorkToMake>18000</WorkToMake>
            <Mass>6</Mass>
        </statBases>
        <costStuffCount>60</costStuffCount>
        <costList>
            <Plasteel>20</Plasteel>
            <ComponentIndustrial>6</ComponentIndustrial>
        </costList>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>handle</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>10</power>
                <cooldownTime>1.8</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>edge</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Cut</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>26</power>
                <cooldownTime>2.4</cooldownTime>
				<armorPenetration>0.4</armorPenetration>
            </li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
  
  <!-- ====================== Chain Shortsword ===================== -->

    <ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_Chainshortsword</defName>
        <label>Short chainsword</label>
        <description>The Militarum Short Chainsword, a compact yet lethal incarnation of close combat prowess in the Astra Militarum's arsenal, symbolizes the Imperium's commitment to versatility and adaptability on the grim battlefields of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nCrafted for maneuverability and ease of use, the short chainsword features a truncated design without compromising its deadly efficiency. Its monomolecular teeth, driven by a high-torque motor, make it a formidable weapon in close-quarters engagements. The shortened length enhances the guardsman's agility, allowing for swift strikes and rapid responses in the heat of melee combat.\n\nIn the hands of the Astra Militarum, the Militarum Short Chainsword becomes a tool of relentless aggression, embodying the gritty determination and resourcefulness of the Imperial Guard. Whether clearing cramped corridors, engaging in urban warfare, or acting as a backup weapon in emergencies, this compact chainsword stands ready to deliver lethal blows against the enemies of the Imperium.\n\nAs the soldiers of the Astra Militarum navigate the treacherous landscapes of the 41st millennium, the Militarum Short Chainsword remains a symbol of adaptability, ensuring that the forces of the Imperium are always prepared for the unpredictable challenges that await them in the dark and war-torn galaxy.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/Chain Shortsword</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <WorkToMake>14000</WorkToMake>
            <Mass>2.25</Mass>
        </statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
      <MoveSpeed>0.10</MoveSpeed>
		</equippedStatOffsets>
        <costStuffCount>50</costStuffCount>
        <costList>
            <Plasteel>16</Plasteel>
            <ComponentIndustrial>4</ComponentIndustrial>
        </costList>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>handle</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>10</power>
                <cooldownTime>1.6</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>edge</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Cut</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>20</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
				<armorPenetration>0.3</armorPenetration>
            </li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
  
   <!-- ====================== Trench Shovel ===================== -->
   
    <ThingDef ParentName="BaseMeleeWeapon_Blunt_Quality">
        <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_TrenchShovel</defName>
        <label>Trench shovel</label>
        <description>The Trench Shovel, revered as the favored close-quarters weapon of the Death Korps of Krieg, epitomizes the grim and relentless nature of the regiments hailing from the irradiated and war-torn planet.\n\nForged in the fires of Krieg's industrial complexes, the Trench Shovel serves as a multi-purpose tool for the Death Korps soldiers. Its sturdy construction allows it to withstand the harsh conditions of trench warfare and close combat. With a reinforced, sharpened blade on one side and a serrated edge on the other, the shovel transforms seamlessly from a digging implement to a formidable melee weapon.\n\nIn the hands of the Death Korps, the Trench Shovel becomes an extension of their unyielding will and unrelenting discipline. Whether it's breaching enemy fortifications, clearing obstacles, or engaging in brutal hand-to-hand combat, the Death Korps soldiers wield the Trench Shovel with ruthless efficiency.\n\nAs the regiments of Krieg march stoically into battle, the haunting echoes of the Trench Shovel striking against enemy armor and fortifications serve as a somber reminder of the brutal warfare endured by the Death Korps on their desolate home world. This utilitarian implement turned lethal weapon embodies the harsh pragmatism and indomitable spirit of the Death Korps of Krieg as they fulfill their duty to the God-Emperor in the grim darkness of the far future.</description>
        <possessionCount>1</possessionCount>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/Trench Shovel</texPath>
            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
        </graphicData>
        <uiIconScale>1.2</uiIconScale>
        <techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
        <statBases>
            <WorkToMake>8000</WorkToMake>
            <Mass>1.5</Mass>
        </statBases>
        <equippedAngleOffset>-65</equippedAngleOffset>
        <recipeMaker>
            <researchPrerequisite>GW_AM_RegimentsOfRenown</researchPrerequisite>
            <skillRequirements>
                <Crafting>4</Crafting>
            </skillRequirements>
            <recipeUsers Inherit="False">
                <li>HP_AM_MilitarumFabricationBench</li>
            </recipeUsers>
            <displayPriority>400</displayPriority>
        </recipeMaker>
        <costStuffCount>50</costStuffCount>
        <costList>
            <WoodLog>60</WoodLog>
        </costList>
        <weaponTags>
            <li>IndustrialMeleeDecent</li>
            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
        </weaponTags>
        <tradeTags>
            <li>HPMelee</li>
            <li>GW_AM_IndustrialMelee</li>
        </tradeTags>
        <weaponClasses>
            <li>Melee</li>
        </weaponClasses>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>handle</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Poke</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>head</label>
                <labelUsedInLogging>false</labelUsedInLogging>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>17.7</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
			<li>
				<label>edge</label>
                <labelUsedInLogging>false</labelUsedInLogging>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Cut</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>18</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
			</li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
	
	<!-- ===== Combat Knife =====-->
	
	<ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CombatKnife</defName>
        <label>Combat knife</label>
        <description>The Militarum Combat Knife, a staple among the Astra Militarum forces, stands as a testament to the practicality and versatility required by soldiers in the unforgiving battlegrounds of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.\n\nForged for durability and precision, the combat knife is a compact yet formidable blade. Its razor-sharp edge is ideal for a range of close-quarters engagements, making it an essential tool for Astra Militarum soldiers navigating the unpredictable landscapes of warfare. The serrated sections along the blade enhance its utility, allowing for effective use in various tactical situations.\n\nThe design of the Militarum Combat Knife incorporates a reinforced hilt and ergonomic grip, ensuring a secure hold even in the chaos of battle. Its compact size makes it a practical sidearm, allowing soldiers to carry it alongside their primary weaponry without hindrance.\n\nWhether used for stealthy incursions, survival situations, or as a last resort in hand-to-hand combat, the Militarum Combat Knife embodies the resilience and adaptability required by the soldiers of the Astra Militarum. In the grim darkness of the 41st millennium, where every inch of ground is contested, the combat knife is a symbol of the indomitable spirit and resourcefulness of the Imperial Guard.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/CombatKnife</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <WorkToMake>3200</WorkToMake>
            <Mass>1.0</Mass>
        </statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
      <MoveSpeed>0.20</MoveSpeed>
		</equippedStatOffsets>
        <costStuffCount>45</costStuffCount>
        <costList>
            <Plasteel>8</Plasteel>
        </costList>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>handle</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>10</power>
                <cooldownTime>1.6</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>edge</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Cut</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>14</power>
                <cooldownTime>1.8</cooldownTime>
				<armorPenetration>0.25</armorPenetration>
            </li>
			<li>
				<label>point</label>
				<capacities>
					<li>Stab</li>
				</capacities>
				<power>15</power>
				<cooldownTime>1.8</cooldownTime>
				<armorPenetration>0.28</armorPenetration>
			</li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
	
	<!-- ===== Catachan Fang =====-->
	
	<ThingDef ParentName="GW_AM_IndustrialSharpBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_MeleeWeapon_CatachanFang</defName>
        <label>Catachan fang</label>
        <description>The Catachan Fang, revered among the mighty Catachan Jungle Fighters, is a deadly and iconic close combat weapon that reflects the raw power and primal skill of these renowned Imperial Guard soldiers.\n\nForged amidst the perilous jungles of Catachan, the Fang boasts a distinctive design. Its blade, crafted from exceptionally durable materials, features a serrated edge reminiscent of the dangers lurking within the dense foliage of Catachan's untamed wilderness. The Fang is not merely a weapon but a symbol of the Jungle Fighters' tenacity and ability to adapt to the formidable challenges they face.\n\nThe balance and heft of the Catachan Fang make it an ideal companion for the close-quarters engagements that Catachan warriors often find themselves entangled in. Its design allows for swift and precise strikes, capable of dealing devastating blows to adversaries in the blink of an eye.\n\nIn the hands of a Catachan Jungle Fighter, the Catachan Fang becomes an extension of the warrior's skill and determination. Whether slashing through dense vegetation or cutting down foes in the heat of battle, the Catachan Fang embodies the untamed spirit of Catachan's formidable soldiers as they defend the Imperium against the myriad threats of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/CatachanKnife</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <WorkToMake>6400</WorkToMake>
            <Mass>1.0</Mass>
        </statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
      <MoveSpeed>0.20</MoveSpeed>
		</equippedStatOffsets>
        <costStuffCount>55</costStuffCount>
        <costList>
            <Plasteel>12</Plasteel>
        </costList>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>handle</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>11</power>
                <cooldownTime>1.6</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>edge</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Cut</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>18</power>
                <cooldownTime>1.8</cooldownTime>
				<armorPenetration>0.36</armorPenetration>
            </li>
			<li>
				<label>point</label>
				<capacities>
					<li>Stab</li>
				</capacities>
				<power>16</power>
				<cooldownTime>1.8</cooldownTime>
				<armorPenetration>0.38</armorPenetration>
			</li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
	
</Defs>
