<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
    <ThingDef Abstract="true" ParentName="BaseGunWithQuality" Name="HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase">
        <techLevel>Spacer</techLevel>
	    <smeltable>False</smeltable>
        <graphicData>
            <graphicClass>Graphic_Single</graphicClass>
        </graphicData>
        <soundInteract>Interact_ChargeRifle</soundInteract>
	    <relicChance>3</relicChance>
        <statBases>
	        <MarketValue>1200</MarketValue>
        </statBases>
        <thingSetMakerTags>
            <li>RewardStandardQualitySuper</li>
        </thingSetMakerTags>
        <tradeTags>
            <li>ExoticMisc</li>
            <li>Artifact</li>
            <li>HPRanged</li>
        </tradeTags>
    </ThingDef>

            <!-- Sanctified Kantrael MG -->

    <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Kantraelsanctified</defName>
        <label>Sanctified Kantrael MG</label>
        <description>In the shadowy corners of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sanctified Kantrael MG emerges as an artifact of unparalleled potency, its name echoing through the annals of the Imperium's grim history. Infused with sacred purpose and bathed in the sanctity of the Emperor's light, this mighty relic stands as a beacon of divine retribution against the myriad threats that beset the Imperium.\n\nThe Sanctified Kantrael MG, a manifestation of the Omnissiah's grace, is a relic of forgotten origin. Its intricately adorned chassis is adorned with sacred inscriptions and symbols, testifying to its consecrated nature. The weapon's components are said to have been blessed by the Tech-Priests of Mars, imbuing it with both mechanical precision and divine fervor.\n\nAs a manifestation of the Machine God's will, the Sanctified Kantrael MG unleashes a hail of righteous fury upon the enemies of the Imperium. Its blessed projectiles, propelled by arcane mechanisms, cut through heretics and xenos alike with unerring accuracy. The unmistakable hum of the weapon's consecrated components adds an otherworldly aura to the cacophony of battle.\n\nIn the hands of a faithful servant of the Imperium, the Sanctified Kantrael MG becomes a divine instrument of purgation, smiting the foes of mankind with relentless zeal. Its sanctified nature marks it as more than a mere weapon—it is a relic, a conduit of the Emperor's wrath, wielded in the eternal struggle against the encroaching darkness of the Warhammer 40,000 galaxy.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/Sanctified Kantrael MG</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <Mass>3.8</Mass>
            <AccuracyTouch>0.65</AccuracyTouch>
            <AccuracyShort>0.80</AccuracyShort>
            <AccuracyMedium>0.90</AccuracyMedium>
            <AccuracyLong>0.85</AccuracyLong>
            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.50</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
        </statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
			<Beauty>5</Beauty> 
        </equippedStatOffsets>
        <weaponClasses>
            <li>LongShots</li>
        </weaponClasses>
        <weaponTags>
            <li>SpacerGun</li>
        </weaponTags>
        <verbs>
            <li>
                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt</defaultProjectile>
                <warmupTime>0.90</warmupTime>
                <range>40.0</range>
                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                <burstShotCount>3</burstShotCount>
                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Kantrael</soundCast>
                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
            </li>
        </verbs>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>stock</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>barrel</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                    <li>Poke</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
  
            <!-- Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine -->

    <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefoursanctified</defName>
        <label>Sanctified MK4 lascarbine</label>
        <description>In the grim and unyielding expanse of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine emerges as a sacred artifact, a symbol of unwavering devotion and the Emperor's divine protection. Crafted with meticulous care and blessed by the Ecclesiarchy, this relic stands as a beacon of faith and righteous fury against the myriad enemies that threaten the Imperium.\n\nThe Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine's origins are shrouded in the mysteries of the Ecclesiarchy's sanctuaries. Its sleek and ornate design, adorned with sacred inscriptions and symbols of purity, signifies its consecrated nature. Each component is said to have been anointed in holy oils and subjected to rituals of benediction, infusing the weapon with the very essence of the Emperor's divine grace.\n\nAs a manifestation of the Emperor's will, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine delivers death to heretics and xenos alike. Its blessed projectiles, propelled by the sanctified mechanisms within, strike with unerring accuracy, leaving a trail of purifying flame in their wake. The weapon's unmistakable discharge echoes the liturgy of the faithful, a symphony of devotion in the heat of battle.\n\nIn the hands of a devoted servant of the Imperium, the Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine becomes a conduit of righteous wrath, purging the enemies of mankind with unrelenting zeal. Its sanctified nature transforms it into more than a mere firearm—it is a relic, a sacred instrument wielded in the eternal struggle to safeguard humanity from the malevolent forces that lurk in the darkness of the Warhammer 40,000 galaxy.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/Sanctified MK4 Lascarbine</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <Mass>3.4</Mass>
            <AccuracyTouch>0.60</AccuracyTouch>
            <AccuracyShort>0.85</AccuracyShort>
            <AccuracyMedium>0.70</AccuracyMedium>
            <AccuracyLong>0.65</AccuracyLong>
            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.15</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
        </statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
			<Beauty>5</Beauty> 
        </equippedStatOffsets>
        <weaponClasses>
            <li>LongShots</li>
        </weaponClasses>
        <weaponTags>
            <li>SpacerGun</li>
        </weaponTags>
        <verbs>
            <li>
                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt</defaultProjectile>
                <warmupTime>0.80</warmupTime>
                <range>30.0</range>
                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>12</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                <burstShotCount>2</burstShotCount>
                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_Lascarbinefour</soundCast>
                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
            </li>
        </verbs>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>stock</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>barrel</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                    <li>Poke</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
  
            <!-- Sanctified Voss MKI -->

    <ThingDef ParentName="HP_AM_SanctifiedLasgunBase">
        <defName>GW_AM_Gun_VossPatternsanctified</defName>
        <label>Sanctified Voss MKI</label>
        <description>In the somber and desolate tapestry of the Warhammer 40,000 universe, the Sanctified Voss MKI stands as a revered artifact, a testament to the indomitable spirit of the Imperium and the unyielding resolve of its defenders. This sacred relic, steeped in the traditions of the Adeptus Mechanicus, embodies the fusion of technology and divine veneration.\n\nForged in the sanctified foundries of Mars, the Sanctified Voss MKI is an intricate masterpiece, its mechanical intricacies meticulously crafted and adorned with arcane symbols of the Machine God's favor. Each component, from its blessed barrel to the sacred firing mechanism, has undergone sacred rites and consecration, elevating it beyond the realm of mundane weaponry.\n\nThe Sanctified Voss MKI operates on the sacred principles of the Omnissiah, delivering bolts of righteous fury with unerring precision. Its blessed projectiles, propelled by the holy machinations within, pierce through the darkness with a luminous trail, leaving naught but purifying flame in their wake. The weapon's discharge resonates like a liturgical hymn, a harmonious symphony of reverence and destruction.\n\nWielded by the faithful Tech-Priests of the Adeptus Mechanicus, the Sanctified Voss MKI becomes a conduit of the Machine God's divine will. Its presence on the battlefield is a manifestation of the Omnissiah's blessings, striking down the enemies of the Imperium with calculated and relentless force. As an artifact, the Sanctified Voss MKI is more than a tool of war—it is a sacred relic, a testament to the enduring alliance between man and machine in the eternal struggle against the darkness that engulfs the galaxy.</description>
        <graphicData>
            <texPath>Weapons/Sanctified Voss MKI</texPath>
        </graphicData>
        <statBases>
            <Mass>3.2</Mass>
            <AccuracyTouch>0.55</AccuracyTouch>
            <AccuracyShort>0.85</AccuracyShort>
            <AccuracyMedium>0.70</AccuracyMedium>
            <AccuracyLong>0.65</AccuracyLong>
            <RangedWeapon_Cooldown>1.0</RangedWeapon_Cooldown>
        </statBases>
		<equippedStatOffsets>
			<Beauty>5</Beauty> 
        </equippedStatOffsets>
        <weaponClasses>
            <li>LongShots</li>
        </weaponClasses>
        <weaponTags>
            <li>SpacerGun</li>
        </weaponTags>
        <verbs>
            <li>
                <verbClass>Verb_Shoot</verbClass>
                <hasStandardCommand>true</hasStandardCommand>
                <defaultProjectile>VWEL_Bullet_Lasbolt</defaultProjectile>
                <warmupTime>1.20</warmupTime>
                <range>34.0</range>
                <ticksBetweenBurstShots>10</ticksBetweenBurstShots>
                <burstShotCount>5</burstShotCount>
                <soundCast>GW_AM_Gun_VossPattern</soundCast>
                <soundCastTail>GunTail_Heavy</soundCastTail>
                <muzzleFlashScale>12</muzzleFlashScale>
            </li>
        </verbs>
        <tools>
            <li>
                <label>stock</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
            <li>
                <label>barrel</label>
                <capacities>
                    <li>Blunt</li>
                    <li>Poke</li>
                </capacities>
                <power>9</power>
                <cooldownTime>2</cooldownTime>
            </li>
        </tools>
    </ThingDef>
</Defs>