<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<Defs>
    <ResearchProjectDef Abstract="True" Name="GW_AM_HoITechBase"  ParentName="GW_ImperiumTechBase">
		<techLevel>Industrial</techLevel>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_TacticaImperium</defName>
		<label>tactica imperium</label>
        <description>In the strategic depths of GrimWorld 40,000, the Tactica Imperium serves as the guiding doctrine for Imperial forces. This comprehensive tactical manual encapsulates the accumulated wisdom of the Imperium in navigating the relentless challenges of the 41st millennium.\n\nBound in weathered and battle-worn tomes, the Tactica Imperium is a symbol of strategic resilience. Its pages, etched with the experiences of countless battles, provide a roadmap for commanders to navigate the complexities of warfare within the Imperium.\n\nWithin its chapters lie the doctrines of combined arms, siege warfare, and adaptable tactics, embodying the pragmatic nature demanded by the grim realities of battle. As a revered text, the Tactica Imperium is a cornerstone of military education, shaping the minds of commanders who lead the Imperium's forces into the unyielding darkness.\n\nIn the relentless struggle of GrimWorld 40,000, the Tactica Imperium stands as a beacon of strategic insight, a vital tool in the Imperium's unending quest for survival and dominance.</description>
        <baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>MicroelectronicsBasics</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>2.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_ImperiumDefense</defName>
		<label>imperium defense</label>
        <description>Within the grim and besieged expanse of GrimWorld 40,000, Imperium Defense stands as a formidable bulwark against the encroaching darkness. With a steadfast commitment to protect the Imperium's domains, this defensive network is a testament to the unwavering resolve of the Imperium in the face of relentless threats.\n\nMarked by towering fortifications and layered defenses, Imperium Defense reflects the pragmatic and resilient nature demanded by the harsh realities of the 41st millennium. Embracing a multifaceted approach, it combines formidable walls, automated turrets, and strategic chokepoints to repel assailants on the battlefield.\n\nStrategically positioned bunkers and bastions bear the scars of countless engagements, each testament to the defenders' unyielding commitment. The defensive architecture, adorned with Imperial iconography, symbolizes the Imperium's unrelenting defiance against those who seek to bring about its demise.\n\nAs a cornerstone of Imperium strategy, Imperium Defense embodies the collective determination to hold the line. In the relentless struggle for survival, it stands as an embodiment of the indomitable spirit that fuels the Imperium's defense against the myriad threats lurking in the grim and perilous expanse of GrimWorld 40,000.</description>
        <baseCost>2000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_TacticaImperium</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_MilitariumArmor</defName>
		<label>militarium armor</label>
        <description>In the war-ravaged landscape of GrimWorld 40,000, Militarum Armor serves as the unyielding shield for Imperial Guard forces. Crafted with pragmatic efficiency and battle-worn resilience, this armor embodies the Imperium's commitment to providing its soldiers with durable protection in the relentless 41st millennium warfare.\n\nConstructed from reinforced ceramite and ablative plating, Militarum Armor is a testament to the imperatives of survival. Its utilitarian design reflects the harsh realities of the battlefield, offering steadfast protection against ballistic and energy threats.\n\nEmblazoned with the Aquila and regimental markings, each suit of Militarum Armor carries the weight of duty and loyalty. The battle-scarred appearance tells stories of countless engagements, symbolizing the sacrifices made by Imperial Guardsmen in service to the Emperor.\n\nEquipped with an integrated rebreather and environmental seals, Militarum Armor ensures the resilience of its wearers against the hazardous conditions of the war-torn worlds they traverse. In the face of relentless adversaries, it stands as a symbol of the Imperium's commitment to defending humanity against the encroaching darkness of GrimWorld 40,000.s</description>
        <baseCost>1000</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_TacticaImperium</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>3.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>3.50</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_RegimentsOfRenown</defName>
		<label>regiments of renown</label>
        <description>In the vast tapestry of GrimWorld 40,000, the Regiments of Renown stand as illustrious symbols of valor and distinction within the Imperial Guard. These elite units, forged in the crucible of countless battles, carry a storied history and exemplify the highest standards of martial prowess and unwavering loyalty to the Imperium.\n\nDistinguished by their unique heraldry, battle honors, and exceptional combat prowess, the Regiments of Renown are the embodiment of the Imperium's finest. Each regiment bears a legacy etched with heroic deeds, serving as a beacon of inspiration for their fellow Guardsmen.\n\nThese elite forces often deploy specialized tactics and wield rare or advanced weaponry, showcasing the Imperium's commitment to harnessing every advantage in the ongoing war. Whether renowned for their unyielding defense, lightning-fast assaults, or strategic brilliance, each regiment contributes its own indelible mark to the Imperium's enduring struggle.\n\nAs legends on the battlefield, the Regiments of Renown inspire awe and fear among allies and adversaries alike. Their stories echo through the grim corridors of Imperial history, reinforcing the Imperium's resilience and determination against the relentless darkness of GrimWorld 40,000.</description>
        <baseCost>500</baseCost>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>2.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

		<!--Regiments-->
    <ResearchProjectDef Abstract="True" Name="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase" ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
        <prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_RegimentsOfRenown</li>
		</prerequisites>
        <baseCost>1500</baseCost>
        <researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
    </ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_Catachan</defName>
		<label>Catachan Jungle Fighters</label>
        <description>In the grim and hostile universe of Warhammer 40,000, the Catachan Jungle Fighters represent a breed of elite soldiers forged on the death world Catachan. Renowned for their exceptional combat skills and resilience, these warriors navigate the perilous jungles with unparalleled expertise.\n\nClad in camouflaged fatigues designed for jungle warfare, Catachan Jungle Fighters seamlessly blend into their surroundings. Their attire is a testament to the harsh conditions of Catachan, emphasizing practicality and adaptability in the face of relentless threats.\n\nExpert practitioners of guerrilla tactics, Catachan Jungle Fighters excel in ambushing enemies and navigating dense foliage with stealth and precision. Armed with rugged weaponry suited for the unpredictable jungles, they turn the natural environment into a deadly weapon against their foes.\n\nEach Catachan warrior carries the scars of surviving Catachan's lethal ecosystem, and their reputation for tenacity and skill has become legendary in the Imperium. In the grim darkness of the 41st millennium, the Catachan Jungle Fighters stand as a symbol of the Imperium's ability to produce elite soldiers capable of thriving in the most hazardous conditions of Warhammer 40,000.</description>
		<researchViewY>0.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_DeathKorpsOfKrieg</defName>
		<label>Death Korps of Krieg</label>
        <description>In the grim and unrelenting universe of Warhammer 40,000, the Death Korps of Krieg stand as a stoic and disciplined regiment within the Imperial Guard. Originating from the irradiated and war-torn Death World of Krieg, these soldiers are marked by their unwavering commitment to duty and the relentless pursuit of victory.\n\nClad in distinctive gas masks and trench coats, the Death Korps of Krieg exhibit a grim and austere appearance. Their attire reflects the harsh conditions of their homeworld, a place perpetually ravaged by warfare and toxic environments.\n\nKnown for their exceptional discipline and resilience, the Death Korps soldiers are relentless in the face of adversity. They are often deployed in trench warfare and siege scenarios, embodying a willingness to endure prolonged conflicts for the glory of the Emperor.\n\nArmed with sturdy lasguns and heavy artillery, the Death Korps of Krieg bring devastating firepower to bear upon their enemies. Their battlefield tactics emphasize attrition and methodical advancement, reflecting the relentless determination instilled in them by the unforgiving crucible of Krieg.\n\nEach soldier of the Death Korps carries the weight of their homeworld's tragic history and the burden of unyielding service to the Imperium. In the grim darkness of the 41st millennium, the Death Korps of Krieg exemplify the harsh realities and unwavering resolve required to defend humanity against the myriad threats of Warhammer 40,000.</description>
		<researchViewY>0.70</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_Mordian</defName>
		<label>Mordian Iron Guard</label>
        <description>In the relentless warfare of Warhammer 40,000, the Mordian Iron Guard stands as a stalwart and disciplined regiment within the Imperial Guard. Hailing from the urban fortress world of Mordian, these soldiers are renowned for their precision, unwavering discipline, and formidable battlefield formations.\n\nClad in distinctive dress uniforms, complete with dress caps and rigidly maintained formations, the Mordian Iron Guard presents a striking and martial appearance. Their attire reflects both the military precision instilled in them and the urban battlegrounds from which they emerge.\n\nKnown for their methodical and synchronized maneuvers, the Mordian Iron Guard excels in line formations and defensive tactics. Their training emphasizes maintaining order and unyielding discipline, creating a formidable force on the battlefield.\n\nArmed with lasguns and supported by heavy weapons teams, the Mordian Iron Guard brings disciplined firepower to bear against their foes. Their strategic approach and cohesive formations make them a resilient and effective force in various combat scenarios.\n\nEach Mordian Iron Guard soldier embodies the regiment's dedication to precision and order, representing the unwavering commitment to defending the Imperium in the grim and expansive universe of Warhammer 40,000.</description>
		<researchViewY>1.25</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_TallarnDesertRaiders</defName>
		<label>Tallarn Desert Raiders</label>
        <description>In the arid expanses of Warhammer 40,000, the Tallarn Desert Raiders epitomize swift and adaptive warfare within the ranks of the Imperial Guard. Hailing from the desert world of Tallarn, these soldiers are renowned for their exceptional mobility, hit-and-run tactics, and mastery of desert warfare.\n\nClad in distinctive desert camouflage and lightweight armor, the Tallarn Desert Raiders seamlessly blend into their sandy surroundings. Their attire reflects both the practical demands of desert combat and the necessity for swift and nimble maneuvers on the battlefield.\n\nKnown for their exceptional speed and flexibility, the Tallarn soldiers excel in hit-and-run tactics and flanking maneuvers. Their expertise in desert warfare allows them to navigate the harsh terrain with ease, turning the vast desert expanse into a tactical advantage.\n\nArmed with lasguns and specializing in fast-moving armored vehicles, the Tallarn Desert Raiders bring rapid and unpredictable firepower to the battlefield. Their hit-and-fade tactics make them a formidable force against adversaries who struggle to keep pace with their agile maneuvers.\n\nEach Tallarn soldier embodies the regiment's adaptability and mastery of desert warfare, showcasing the Imperium's ability to produce specialized forces tailored to the unique challenges of the Warhammer 40,000 universe.</description>
		<researchViewY>1.80</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_TempestusScions</defName>
		<label>Tempestus Scions</label>
        <description>In the relentless and perilous universe of Warhammer 40,000, the Tempestus Scions stand as elite shock troops within the Imperial Guard. Formerly known as Stormtroopers, these soldiers are an elite and highly specialized force, embodying precision, versatility, and unwavering discipline.\n\nClad in distinctive carapace armor, adorned with respirators and rebreather masks, the Tempestus Scions present a formidable and sleek appearance. Their attire reflects both advanced technology and the need for protection in a wide range of hazardous environments.\n\nRenowned for their rapid deployment and surgical strikes, the Tempestus Scions excel in high-stakes missions where precision and speed are paramount. Their training and equipment make them ideal for infiltration, assassination, and combating highly specialized threats to the Imperium.\n\nArmed with hot-shot lasguns and specialized weaponry, the Tempestus Scions bring potent firepower to the battlefield. Whether dropping from low orbit or infiltrating behind enemy lines, they are a force to be reckoned with, capable of turning the tide of battle with their expertise.\n\nEach Tempestus Scion is a symbol of the Imperium's commitment to producing highly trained and adaptable shock troops, ready to face the myriad threats that lurk in the grim darkness of the 41st millennium in Warhammer 40,000.</description>
		<researchViewY>2.45</researchViewY>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="GW_Frame.DefModExtension_ExtraPrerequisiteActions">
                <StudyLocation>GW_Cogitator</StudyLocation>
                <ItemStudyRequirements>
                    <li Class="GW_Frame.StudyRequirement">
                        <StudyObject>GW_STC_Fragment</StudyObject>
                        <NumberRequired>1</NumberRequired>
                    </li>    
                </ItemStudyRequirements>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_Valhallan</defName>
		<label>Valhallan Ice Warriors</label>
        <description>In the frozen wastelands of Warhammer 40,000, the Valhallan Ice Warriors stand as stalwart defenders within the Imperial Guard. Originating from the ice-covered world of Valhalla, these soldiers are renowned for their resilience, adaptability to extreme cold, and unyielding determination.\n\nCloaked in rugged winter gear, including fur-lined coats and ice-resistant armor, the Valhallan Ice Warriors present a distinctive and practical appearance. Their attire reflects not only the harsh conditions of Valhalla but also the necessity for effective protection against the biting cold.\n\nKnown for their ability to endure freezing temperatures and expert marksmanship, the Valhallan soldiers excel in winter warfare. Their training and equipment make them well-suited for prolonged operations in frigid environments, turning the icy landscape into a tactical advantage.\n\nArmed with lasguns and heavy weapons, the Valhallan Ice Warriors bring potent firepower to bear against their foes. Their strategic approach and adaptation to cold climates make them a formidable force in both defensive and offensive scenarios.\n\nEach Valhallan soldier embodies the regiment's resilience and adaptability, showcasing the Imperium's capacity to produce specialized forces ready to face the harsh realities of the 41st millennium in Warhammer 40,000.</description>
		<researchViewY>3.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_VostoyanFirstborn</defName>
		<label>Vostoyan Firstborn</label>
        <description>In the sprawling expanse of Warhammer 40,000, the Vostroyan Firstborn stand as a distinguished regiment within the Imperial Guard. Hailing from the hive world of Vostroya, these soldiers are renowned for their regal appearance, formidable discipline, and exceptional marksmanship.\n\nAdorned in elaborate carapace armor and distinctive uniforms, the Vostroyan Firstborn present a striking and aristocratic appearance. Their attire reflects not only a commitment to practical protection but also a nod to the regal traditions of their homeworld.\n\nKnown for their precision in marksmanship and methodical tactics, the Vostroyan soldiers excel in long-range engagements. Their training emphasizes disciplined fire and cohesive unit movements, making them a formidable force on the battlefield.\n\nArmed with lasguns and ornate weaponry, the Vostroyan Firstborn bring a blend of sophistication and lethal firepower to their adversaries. Their strategic approach and disciplined formations make them adept at both defensive and offensive operations.\n\nEach Vostroyan soldier embodies the regiment's proud heritage and commitment to excellence, symbolizing the Imperium's capacity to produce specialized forces ready to face the myriad challenges of the grim darkness in the 41st millennium.</description>
		<researchViewY>3.60</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_CadianShockTroops</defName>
		<label>Kasrkin Elite Troops</label>
        <description>In the unforgiving expanse of Warhammer 40,000, the Kasrkin stand as elite troops within the Imperial Guard, renowned for their specialized training and unwavering discipline. These soldiers, often deployed in critical missions, embody the pinnacle of Imperial Guard infantry, combining advanced skills with superior firepower.\n\nAdorned in distinctive carapace armor, the Kasrkin present a formidable and visually striking appearance. Their attire, marked by the Aquila and regimental insignia, reflects the high standard of protection and the pride associated with their elite status.\n\nKnown for their advanced combat tactics and resilience, the Kasrkin excel in various battlefield scenarios. Whether engaging in urban warfare, counterinsurgency operations, or frontline assaults, they showcase adaptability and strategic prowess.\n\nArmed with potent hot-shot lasguns and equipped with specialized gear, the Kasrkin bring formidable and precise firepower to the forefront. Their role often involves tackling high-priority targets, and their advanced training allows them to operate in small, elite squads with efficiency.\n\nEach Kasrkin soldier embodies the Imperium's commitment to producing an elite force capable of undertaking critical missions in the grim and perilous reality of the 41st millennium.</description>
		<researchViewY>4.20</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

    <ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_RegimentResearchBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_SteelLegion</defName>
		<label>Armageddon Steel Legion</label>
        <description>In the war-torn realms of Warhammer 40,000, the Armageddon Steel Legion stands as a disciplined and mechanized regiment within the Imperial Guard. Hailing from the industrial world of Armageddon, these soldiers are renowned for their resilience, combined arms tactics, and adaptability in urban warfare.\n\nClad in distinctive gas masks, flak armor, and armored fatigues, the Armageddon Steel Legion presents a rugged and utilitarian appearance. Their attire reflects both the harsh conditions of urban warfare and the necessity for protection against various threats.\n\nKnown for their proficiency in mechanized warfare and armored assaults, the Armageddon Steel Legion excels in deploying heavy infantry alongside formidable armored support. Their training emphasizes combined arms tactics, making them a versatile force capable of engaging in a wide range of battlefield scenarios.\n\nArmed with lasguns and supported by armored vehicles, including Chimera transports and Leman Russ tanks, the Armageddon Steel Legion brings a potent mix of infantry and heavy firepower to the battlefield. Their ability to conduct coordinated mechanized assaults makes them effective in reclaiming urban territories from hostile forces.\n\nEach Armageddon Steel Legionnaire embodies the regiment's commitment to defending their homeworld and the Imperium at large, showcasing the adaptability and resilience required to thrive in the grim darkness of the 41st millennium.</description>
		<researchViewY>4.80</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

			<!--Abhumans-->
	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_AbhumanIntegration</defName>
		<label>abhuman integration</label>
        <description>In the expansive lore of Warhammer 40,000, "Abhumans" is a collective term used to describe various non-standard human strains or subspecies that have evolved under different environmental conditions or circumstances. These Abhumans exhibit distinct physical and genetic traits that set them apart from the baseline human population.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_MilitariumArmor</li>
		</prerequisites>
        <baseCost>500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>4.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.70</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_OgrynIntegration</defName>
		<label>ogryn integration</label>
        <description>Allows for the creation of equipment usually wielded by Ogryn, massive abhumans usually employed as shock troopers by the Imperium of Man. The Ogryn (Homo sapiens gigantus) are a huge and physically powerful Abhuman mutant subspecies of Humanity, often employed by the Imperium of Man as shock troopers in the Astra Militarum's Militarum Auxilla. Ogryns possess many traits prized by the Imperium; they are brutally strong and completely loyal, although extremely limited intellectually, which restricts their battlefield role to simple and direct assaults. They hail from a series of cold and barren planets across the galaxy that possess high gravity, such as Anark Zeta, which is why they appear larger, heavier and bulkier compared to baseline Humans. Ogryns compensate for their mental deficiencies with overwhelming physicality -- the brutish creatures stand around 10 Terran feet (3 metres) tall and can shrug off wounds that would kill an Imperial Guardsman several times over. These qualities mean that Ogryns make exceptional shock troops, and are often deployed on the front lines of battle by Imperial commanders.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_AbhumanIntegration</li>
		</prerequisites>
        <baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>5.40</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>

	<ResearchProjectDef ParentName="GW_AM_HoITechBase">
		<defName>GW_AM_RatlingIntegration</defName>
		<label>ratling integration</label>
        <description>Allows for the creation of equipment usually wielded by Ratlings, small abhumans usually employed as snipers by the Imperium of Man. A Ratling (Homo sapiens minimus) is a member of a small, loud, hungry and lecherous Abhuman species. Ratlings are granted full Imperial citizenship despite their mutant status and in the past have often served in the regiments of the Astra Militarum as members of the Militarum Auxilla. However, they are still distrusted by the more Puritanical members of the Inquisition. Though less resilient than their baseline Human comrades, Ratlings are naturally excellent shots. It is said that Ratling marksmen can take the head off a Heretic from over a kilometre away. Coupled with their knack for staying out of harm's way, this makes Ratlings formidable snipers who can exact a withering toll upon superior enemy forces. Inevitably, the Abhuman Ratlings face prejudice from the baseline Human troops they serve alongside, yet their skill as thieves, fences and black marketeers tends to win them acceptance. Indeed, Guardsmen who give the Ratlings too much grief will often find themselves mysteriously short of ammunition in the heat of battle, while their diminutive tormentors watch gleefully through telescopic sights.</description>
		<prerequisites>
			<li>GW_AM_AbhumanIntegration</li>
		</prerequisites>
        <baseCost>1500</baseCost>
		<researchViewX>5.00</researchViewX>
		<researchViewY>6.00</researchViewY>
	</ResearchProjectDef>
</Defs>
